Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995 UE.4.1.6
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals
1936-1995
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE.4.1.6
15.6 Linear Feet
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 6 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
(13 boxes)
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995, UE.4.1.6, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
District 6 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) consisted of locals throughout western Pennsylvania and West Virginia and are now part of the UE's Eastern Region. This series contains files on UE District 6 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 6. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Related Material
UE District 6 Records, 1940s-1980s, UE.15.6, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 506 Records, 1940-1980s, UE.16.506, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 601, East Pittsburgh, Pa. Records, 1947-1954, UE.16.601, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine & Furniture Workers Local 601 Records, 1939-1988, AIS.1989.16, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 610 Records, 1937-1990, UE.16.610, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 618 Records, 1960s, UE.16.618, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 647 Records, 1989-1990, UE.16.647, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Pennyslvania -- History -- 20th century; Labor; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- History; Emspak, Julius; Matles, James J.; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 6; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
- District 6, 1.
  - District 6 Proposed Constitutional Amendments, November 24, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - District 6 President Logan Burkhart Correspondence, October 27, 1937, January 16, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Logan Burkhart to Whom it May Concern Regarding Reduced Hours and the Labor Party, October 27, 1937; 1. (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Burkhart Report of District 6 Regarding Unemployment and District Organization, January 16, 1938; 2. (Box 1, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - District 6 President Michael Fitzpatrick Correspondence, July 30, 1941- July 7, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Michael Fitzpatrick to All Local Union Presidents Regarding Taxation and Political Action, July 30, 1941; 1. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Fitzpatrick to All Western Pennsylvania Congressmen Regarding Taxation, August 1, 1941; 2. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Fitzpatrick to All District 6 Local Presidents Regarding World War II with Fitzpatrick Telegram to Franklin Roosevelt, December 10, 1941; 3. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Fitzpatrick to All District 6 Local Presidents Regarding Defense Agencies, Rent and Pennsylvania CIO Political Action, January 29, 1942; 4. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Philip Murray Regarding AFL-CIO Inter-Union Relations, January 1942; 5. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Donald Nelson Regarding Productivity with Resolution on Production Councils, March 1942; 6. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Fitzpatrick Telegram to Ways and Means Committee Regarding Taxation, May 1942; 7. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Fitzpatrick to Congressmen Weiss, et al. Regarding Taxation, June 25, 1942; 8. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Fitzpatrick to Minority Members of the Ways and Means Committee Regarding Taxation, June 25, 1942; 9. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Fitzpatrick to All UE Locals Regarding Taxation and Political Action, June 25, 1942; 10. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Fitzpatrick to All Dictrict 6 Local Presidents Regarding Local 615 Pittsburgh Equitable Meter Strike, July 8, 1942; 11. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - Fitzpatrick to Locals 601, et al. Regarding Organization at Mine Safety Appliances and World War II, July 7, 1943; 12. (Box 1, Folder 3, Item 12)
  - District 6 President Thomas Fitzpatrick Correspondence, December 26, 1945 - August 27, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Thomas Fitzpatrick to Local 506 President, et al. Regarding General Electric and Westinghouse Strikes, December 26, 1945; 1. (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Fitzpatrick to All District 6 Locals Regarding PEPC and Political Action, May 28, 1947; 2. (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Fitzpatrick to All District 6 Locals Regarding Taft-Hartley and Political Action, May 28, 1947; 3. (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Fitzpatrick to All District 6 Locals Regarding PAC, June 30, 1947; 4. (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Fitzpatrick to All District 6 Locals Regarding Housing with Letter Regarding Organization of Tenets to Save Homes in Projects, July 14, 1947; 5. (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Fitzpatrick Regarding 1947 UE Convention Delegate Elections and Factionalism, August 27, 1947; 6. (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - District 6 President Stanley Loney Correspondence, January 30, 1948 - April 9, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Stanley Loney to Brothers and Sisters Regarding Factionalism with January 29, 1948, Memorandum of District Meeting, January 30, 1948; 1. (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Loney to Brothers and Sisters Regarding Factionalism with February 1, 1948, Pittsburgh Press Clipping; February 2, 1948, New York Post "Inside Labor" Clipping by Victor Riesel; and February 16, 1948, Stanley Loney Letter to Earl Fox, 2. (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Loney to Sirs and Brothers Regarding Taft-Hartley, March 19, 1948; 3. (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Loney to All District 6 Locals Regarding Mundt-Nixon Bill with Pamphlet "CIO Asks Defeat of Mundt-Nixon Bill", May 12, 1948; 4. (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Loney to Shop Stewards Regarding Speed-Ups, Unemployment, CIO, Taft-Hartely and Wages with Wages and Disruption Pamphlet, April 1, 1949; 5. (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Loney to All District 6 UE Locals Regarding Wages and Westinghouse with Duplicate Statement of UE District 6 Westinghouse Local Unions, February 13, 1951; 6. (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Loney to All Locals Regarding Wages and Wage Stabilization Board with Loney Letter to All AFL, CIO and Independent Unions, February 19, 1951; 7. (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Loney to All Staff Members Regarding Political Action, April 9, 1951; 8. (Box 1, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - District 6 President Stanley Loney Correspondence, December 18, 1951 - September 11, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Stanley Loney to All Local Unions Regarding UE Fighting Fund, December 18, 1951; 1. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Loney to All Staff Members Regarding Local 601 Nuttall Westinghouse Strike, June 23, 1952; 2. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Loney to All Locals Regarding Local 601 Nuttall Westinghouse Strike, April 29, 1952; 3. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Loney to All Local Unions Regarding Local 601 Nuttall Westinghouse Strike, September 8, 1952; 4. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 4)
    - Loney to All Locals and Staff Regarding Allan McNeil Case and Anti-Communism with Some Actions from the Case, October 16, 1952; 5. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 5)
    - Loney to All District 6 Locals Regarding Factionalism, January 28, 1953; 6. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 6)
    - Loney to All Locals Regarding Taft-Hartley with the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia Civil Action No. 5286-52 Decision, February 3, 1953; 7. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 7)
    - Loney to All Local Unions Regarding the Korean War and Reconversion, April 6, 1953; 8. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 8)
    - Loney to All Local Unions Regarding the Allen McNeil Case and Deportations, April 8, 1953; 9. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 9)
    - Loney to All UE Districts Regarding the Allen McNeil Case and Anti-Communism, April 29, 1953; 10. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 10)
    - Loney to All Local Unions Regarding the Allen McNeil Case and Anti-Communism, April 30, 1953; 11. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 11)
    - Loney Regarding Fascism with March 24, 1945, Army Talk and Orientation Fact Sheet 64, June 12, 1953; 12. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 12)
    - Loney to All Local Unions Regarding the Allen McNeil Case and Anti-Communism, September 11, 1953; 13. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 13)
    - Loney to All Local Unions Regarding Local 663 DeLuxe Metal Furniture Strike, September 11, 1953; 14. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 14)
    - Loney to All Officers and Stewards Regarding Wages and CIO, 15. (Box 1, Folder 6, Item 15)
  - District 6 President Daniel Marguriet Correspondence, January 12, 1954 - December 23, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Daniel Marguriet to All Local Unions Regarding Anti-Communism, Joseph McCarthy and General Electric, January 12, 1954; 1. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Marguriet to All Local Officers Regarding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, March 11, 1955; 2. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Marguriet to All Staff Members Regarding Executive Board Meeting with Marguriet Letter to All Executive Board Members, March 18, 1955; 3. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - Marguriet to All Local Unions Regarding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry, March 23, 1955; 4. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - Marguriet to George Leader Regarding Unemployment Compensation and Taxation, April 26, 1955; 5. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 5)
    - Marguriet to All Local Unions Regarding Brownell-Butler Citation, December 23, 1955; 6. (Box 1, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - District 6 President Daniel Marguriet Correspondence, January 4, 1956 - October 16, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - District 6 President Daniel Marguriet Correspondence, December 22, 1975 - March 14, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - District 6 Secretary William Chambers Correspondence, July 29, 1941 - January 30, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - William Chambers to Lyle Dowling Regarding Political Action and Taxation with July 28, 1941, Michael Fitzpatrick Telegram to Benjamin Jarrett, et al., July 29, 1941; 1. (Box 1, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Chambers to All Recording Secretaries Regarding Supplies, November 11, 1941; 2. (Box 1, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - Chambers to All Officers and Stewards Regarding Taxation, January 30, 1942; 3. (Box 1, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - District 6 Secretary Alfred Oyler Correspondence, April 12, 1944 - August 20, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Alfred Oyler to All District 6 Council Delegates Regarding Council Meeting, April 12, 1944; 1. (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - Oyler to All Local Presidents Regarding Veterans and Political Action, August 20, 1945; 2. (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - District 6 Secretary Harry Phelps to All District Council Delegates Regarding Inter-Union Rivalry, May 24, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - District 6 International Representative Leo Turner Correspondence, December 1, 1943 - July 7, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak Regarding District 6 Report, December 1, 1943; 1. (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Turner to Emspak Regarding District 6 Report, February 2, 1944; 2. (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Turner to Emspak Regarding District 6 Report, April 14, 1944; 3. (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 3)
    - Turner to Emspak Regarding District 6 Report, July 7, 1944; 4. (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 4)
  - District 6 International Representative Charles Newell Correspondence, August 16, 1949 - December 27, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Charles Newell to National Officers Regarding Factionalism, 1949 UE Convention Delegates Election and ACTU with August 14, 1949, St. Regis Church Sunday Bulletin, August 16, 1949; 1. (Box 1, Folder 14, Item 1)
    - Newell to All Staff Members, December 27, 1950; 2. (Box 1, Folder 14, Item 2)
  - District 6 International Representative Richard Niebur Correspondence, November 19, 1952 - May 25, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Richard Niebur to District 6 Staff Members Regarding Organization, November 19, 1952; 1. (Box 1, Folder 15, Item 1)
    - Niebur to All Staff Members Regarding Staff Meeting, April 5, 1954; 2. (Box 1, Folder 15, Item 2)
    - Niebur to All Staff Members Regarding Brownell Bill, May 25, 1954; 3. (Box 1, Folder 15, Item 3)
  - District 6 Representative Allen McNeil Regarding Anti-Communism and UE Defense Committee, January 20, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - District 6 Correspondence, January 4, 1956 - November 20, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - District 6 Pittsburgh, Pa., Correspondence, January 4, 1956 - June 5, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - District 6 Correspondence, December 13, 1967 - November 6, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - District 6 Pension Correspondence, November 15, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, May 2, 1937 - May 3, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, May 25 - June 29, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, July 27 - August 24, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, October 26 - November 23, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, June 28 - July 26, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, September 27, 1942 - May 3, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, June 27 - October 24, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, November 28, 1943 - February 27, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, March 26 - May 28, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, July 23 - October 22, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, December 3, 1944 - April 8, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, July 22 -September 23, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, November 25, 1945 - June 23, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, July 28 - October 27, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, November 24, 1946 - May 25, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, July 27, 1947 - January 25, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Council Minutes with July 25, 1947, Clyde Johnson Letters to Thomas Fitzpatrick and Joseph Schoteff, July 27, 1947; 1. (Box 1, Folder 36, Item 1)
    - Council Minutes, October 5, 1947; 2. (Box 1, Folder 36, Item 2)
    - Council Minutes, November 30, 1947; 3. (Box 1, Folder 36, Item 3)
    - Council Minutes with January 29, 1945, Stanley Loney Letter to Delegates, January 25, 1948; 4. (Box 1, Folder 36, Item 4)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, March 21 - September 26, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, November 28, 1948 - March 27, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, May 23 - July 24, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Council Minutes, May 23, 1949; 1. (Box 1, Folder 39, Item 1)
    - Council Minutes with Transcription of Proceedings at District 6 Council Meeting, July 24, 1949; 2. (Box 1, Folder 39, Item 2)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, September 25, 1949 - September 24, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Council Minutes, September 25, 1949; 1. (Box 1, Folder 40, Item 1)
    - Council Minutes with Report on Loyalty, January 29, 1950; 2. (Box 1, Folder 40, Item 2)
    - Council Minutes, July 30, 1950; 3. (Box 1, Folder 40, Item 3)
    - Council Minutes, September 24, 1950; 4. (Box 1, Folder 40, Item 4)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, January 21 - December 2, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, January 27 - September 28, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Council Minutes with January 31, 1952, Stanley Loney Letters to Albert Fitzgerald and Wavil See, January 27, 1952; 1. (Box 1, Folder 42, Item 1)
    - Council Minutes with Note Serial Number 19 Regarding McCarran-Walters Act, March 22, 1952; 2. (Box 1, Folder 42, Item 2)
    - Council Minutes with March 11, 1952, Letter Regarding Detroit Un-American Activities Committee, March 30, 1952; 3. (Box 1, Folder 42, Item 3)
    - Council Minutes, May 25, 1952; 4. (Box 1, Folder 42, Item 4)
    - Council Minutes, July 27, 1952; 5. (Box 1, Folder 42, Item 5)
    - Council Minutes with October 3, 1952, Bob Note to James Matles, September 28,1952; 6. (Box 1, Folder 42, Item 6)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, January 25, 1953 - April 25, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, August 15, 1954 - October 30, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Council Minutes, August 15, 1954; 1. (Box 1, Folder 44, Item 1)
    - Duplicate Council Minutes, October 24, 1954; 2. (Box 1, Folder 44, Item 2)
    - Council Minutes, January 30, 1955; 3. (Box 1, Folder 44, Item 3)
    - Council Minutes, April 24, 1955; 4. (Box 1, Folder 44, Item 4)
    - Council Minutes with August 9, 1955, Daniel Marguriet Letters to John Clark and Herbert Brownell, August 7, 1955; 5. (Box 1, Folder 44, Item 5)
    - Duplicate Council Minutes, October 30, 1955; 6. (Box 1, Folder 44, Item 6)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, March 28, 1955 - October 28, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, June 22, 1968 - June 26, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, October 30, 1971 - October 26, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, October 26, 1974 - October 27, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - District 6 Council Minutes, February 23, 1980 - May 14, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - District 6 Council Resolutions, August 28, 1938 - August 24, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Resolution to Block Attempts of Employers to Use Wage-Hour Laws as Excuse for Wage Cuts, August 28, 1938; 1. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Resolution on Erie, PA, Continental Rubber Strike, May 4, 1941; 2. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Resolution on Allis-Chalmers Collective Bargaining, May 4, 1941; 3. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Resolution on CIO West Penn Hospital Strike, May 4, 1941; 4. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Resolution on Keeping America Out of War in Europe, May 4, 1941; 5. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Resolution on Defending Union Gains and Living Standards Regarding Taxation and Public Assistance, May 25, 1941; 6. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Resolution on Threat of War to America, May 25, 1941; 7. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Resolution on United Mine Workers Struggle for Equal Pay in North and South, May 25, 1941; 8. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Resolution on Women's Wage Differential, May 25, 1941; 9. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Resolution Regarding Strike Legislation, June 29, 1941; 10. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Resolution Regarding Taxation, June 29, 1941; 11. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Resolution Regarding UE Constitutions and Anti-Communism, June 29, 1941; 12. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Resolution on Endorsing Aid to Britain, Russia and China, August 24, 1941; 13. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Resolution on UE Program to Prevent Lay-Offs and Production Curtailment, August 24, 1941; 14. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Resolution on Legislation to Fix Wage Levels, August 24, 1941; 15. (Box 2, Folder 1, Item 15)
  - District 6 Council Resolutions, August 1941 - June 28, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Resolution on Supporting Imperial Strikes, August 1941; 1. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Resolution on the Veto of Moul-Woodring Milk Bill, August 1941; 2. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Resolution on Protecting the Welfare of Conscripts, October 1941; 3. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Resolution on Price Control, October 1941; 4. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Resolution on Wage Freezing, October 1941; 5. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Resolution on Tax Legislation, December 1941; 6. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Resolution on Harry Bridges Deportation Case, December 1941; 7. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Resolution on UE Locals and Defense Councils, January 1942; 8. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Resolution Regarding the Program on Rent Raises, January 1942; 9. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - Resolution on Aid to the War Effort in the Shops, January 1942; 10. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - Resolution on International Labor Cooperation, May 24, 1942; 11. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - Resolution on All Labor Conference for Victory Now, June 28, 1942; 12. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - Resolution on John L. Lewis, June 28, 1942; 13. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - Resolution on Harry Bridges Regarding Deportation, June 28, 1942; 14. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - Resolution on Pittsburgh Area Rent Administrator, June 28, 1942; 15. (Box 2, Folder 2, Item 15)
  - District 6 Council Resolutions, July 26, 1942 - January 16, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Resolution on a Second Front in Europe, July 26, 1942; 1. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Resolution on Polish-Soviet Controversy, May 2, 1943; 2. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Resolution on Supporting Miners and Action of President, May 2, 1943; 3. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Resolution on Supporting President Roosevelt's Casablanca Decision, May 2, 1943; 4. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Resolution on Leadership of CIO President Philip Murray, May 23, 1943; 5. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Resolution on United States Foreign Policy, May 23, 1943; 6. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Resolution on the Detroit "Insurrection", June 27, 1943; 7. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Resolution on Price Control, June 27, 1943; 8. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 8)
    - Resolution on Wages Regarding Little Steel Formula, November 28, 1943; 9. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Resolution on UE Wage Proposals in the Industry, January 16, 1944; 10. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Resolution on the Effective Right to Vote for Soldiers with January 25, 1944, Harold Briney Letter to All Congressmen and UE Districts, January 16, 1944; 11. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 11)
    - Resolution on President Roosevelt's Message to Congress with January 25, 1944, Michael Fitzpatrick Letter to Franklin Roosevelt, January 16, 1944; 12. (Box 2, Folder 3, Item 12)
  - District 6 Council Resolutions, March 26, 1944 - November 25, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Resolution on Negro Discrimination in Baseball, March 26, 1944; 1. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Resolution on 4th Term For President Roosevelt, March 26, 1944; 2. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Resolution on Labor Education, May 28, 1944; 3. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Resolution on No-Strike Pledge, October 22, 1944; 4. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Resolution Regarding Henry Wallace, January 28, 1945; 5. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Resolution on Labor-Management Cooperation in the Post-War Period, April 8, 1945; 6. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Resolution on Fair Employment Practices, April 8, 1945; 7. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - Resolution on San Francisco Conference, April 8, 1945; 8. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - Resolution on the Ball-Burton-Hatch Bill, July 22, 1945; 9. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Resolution on United Nations Charter, July 22, 1945; 10. (Box 2, Folder 4, Item 10)